{"0": {"question": "Andie is a mechanical engineer by training. During college, Andie used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Andie is a consultant for the British Museum and builds model airplanes as a hobby.", "Andie is a consultant for the British Museum."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "builds model airplanes as a hobby"], "work 1": ["A", "is a consultant for the British Museum"], "hobby 1": ["S", "used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["S", "is a mechanical engineer by training"], "name": ["S", "Andie"]}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, "1": {"question": "Ari has a PhD in applied maths. During college, Ari used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Ari is a consultant for the British Museum and builds model airplanes as a hobby.", "Ari is a consultant for the British Museum."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "builds model airplanes as a hobby"], "work 1": ["A", "is a consultant for the British Museum"], "hobby 1": ["S", "used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["S", "has a PhD in applied maths"], "name": ["S", "Ari"]}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, "2": {"question": "Brook is a mechanical engineer by training. During college, Brook flew high-end drones for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Brook is a consultant for the British Museum and builds model airplanes as a hobby.", "Brook is a consultant for the British Museum."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "builds model airplanes as a hobby"], "work 1": ["A", "is a consultant for the British Museum"], "hobby 1": ["S", "flew high-end drones for fun"], "training 1": ["S", "is a mechanical engineer by training"], "name": ["S", "Brook"]}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, "3": {"question": "Dawson has a PhD in applied maths. During college, Dawson flew high-end drones for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Dawson is a consultant for the British Museum and builds model airplanes as a hobby.", "Dawson is a consultant for the British Museum."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "builds model airplanes as a hobby"], "work 1": ["A", "is a consultant for the British Museum"], "hobby 1": ["S", "flew high-end drones for fun"], "training 1": ["S", "has a PhD in applied maths"], "name": ["S", "Dawson"]}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, "4": {"question": "Cameron is a mechanical engineer by training. During college, Cameron used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Cameron is an advisor to the Minister of Culture and builds model airplanes as a hobby.", "Cameron is an advisor to the Minister of Culture."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "builds model airplanes as a hobby"], "work 1": ["A", "is an advisor to the Minister of Culture"], "hobby 1": ["S", "used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["S", "is a mechanical engineer by training"], "name": ["S", "Cameron"]}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, "5": {"question": "Perry has a PhD in applied maths. During college, Perry used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Perry is an advisor to the Minister of Culture and builds model airplanes as a hobby.", "Perry is an advisor to the Minister of Culture."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "builds model airplanes as a hobby"], "work 1": ["A", "is an advisor to the Minister of Culture"], "hobby 1": ["S", "used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["S", "has a PhD in applied maths"], "name": ["S", "Perry"]}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, "6": {"question": "Riley is a mechanical engineer by training. During college, Riley flew high-end drones for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Riley is an advisor to the Minister of Culture and builds model airplanes as a hobby.", "Riley is an advisor to the Minister of Culture."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "builds model airplanes as a hobby"], "work 1": ["A", "is an advisor to the Minister of Culture"], "hobby 1": ["S", "flew high-end drones for fun"], "training 1": ["S", "is a mechanical engineer by training"], "name": ["S", "Riley"]}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, "7": {"question": "Sawyer has a PhD in applied maths. During college, Sawyer flew high-end drones for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Sawyer is an advisor to the Minister of Culture and builds model airplanes as a hobby.", "Sawyer is an advisor to the Minister of Culture."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "builds model airplanes as a hobby"], "work 1": ["A", "is an advisor to the Minister of Culture"], "hobby 1": ["S", "flew high-end drones for fun"], "training 1": ["S", "has a PhD in applied maths"], "name": ["S", "Sawyer"]}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, "8": {"question": "Sloan is a mechanical engineer by training. During college, Sloan used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Sloan is a consultant for the British Museum and plays Go, during spare time.", "Sloan is a consultant for the British Museum."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "plays Go, during spare time"], "work 1": ["A", "is a consultant for the British Museum"], "hobby 1": ["S", "used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["S", "is a mechanical engineer by training"], "name": ["S", "Sloan"]}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, "9": {"question": "Rowan has a PhD in applied maths. During college, Rowan used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Rowan is a consultant for the British Museum and plays Go, during spare time.", "Rowan is a consultant for the British Museum."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "plays Go, during spare time"], "work 1": ["A", "is a consultant for the British Museum"], "hobby 1": ["S", "used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["S", "has a PhD in applied maths"], "name": ["S", "Rowan"]}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, "10": {"question": "Jude is a mechanical engineer by training. During college, Jude flew high-end drones for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Jude is a consultant for the British Museum and plays Go, during spare time.", "Jude is a consultant for the British Museum."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "plays Go, during spare time"], "work 1": ["A", "is a consultant for the British Museum"], "hobby 1": ["S", "flew high-end drones for fun"], "training 1": ["S", "is a mechanical engineer by training"], "name": ["S", "Jude"]}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, "11": {"question": "Maxwell has a PhD in applied maths. During college, Maxwell flew high-end drones for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Maxwell is a consultant for the British Museum and plays Go, during spare time.", "Maxwell is a consultant for the British Museum."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "plays Go, during spare time"], "work 1": ["A", "is a consultant for the British Museum"], "hobby 1": ["S", "flew high-end drones for fun"], "training 1": ["S", "has a PhD in applied maths"], "name": ["S", "Maxwell"]}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, "12": {"question": "River is a mechanical engineer by training. During college, River used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["River is an advisor to the Minister of Culture and plays Go, during spare time.", "River is an advisor to the Minister of Culture."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "plays Go, during spare time"], "work 1": ["A", "is an advisor to the Minister of Culture"], "hobby 1": ["S", "used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["S", "is a mechanical engineer by training"], "name": ["S", "River"]}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, "13": {"question": "Morgan has a PhD in applied maths. During college, Morgan used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Morgan is an advisor to the Minister of Culture and plays Go, during spare time.", "Morgan is an advisor to the Minister of Culture."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "plays Go, during spare time"], "work 1": ["A", "is an advisor to the Minister of Culture"], "hobby 1": ["S", "used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["S", "has a PhD in applied maths"], "name": ["S", "Morgan"]}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, "14": {"question": "Nicky is a mechanical engineer by training. During college, Nicky flew high-end drones for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Nicky is an advisor to the Minister of Culture and plays Go, during spare time.", "Nicky is an advisor to the Minister of Culture."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "plays Go, during spare time"], "work 1": ["A", "is an advisor to the Minister of Culture"], "hobby 1": ["S", "flew high-end drones for fun"], "training 1": ["S", "is a mechanical engineer by training"], "name": ["S", "Nicky"]}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, "15": {"question": "Tyler has a PhD in applied maths. During college, Tyler flew high-end drones for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Tyler is an advisor to the Minister of Culture and plays Go, during spare time.", "Tyler is an advisor to the Minister of Culture."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["S", "plays Go, during spare time"], "work 1": ["A", "is an advisor to the Minister of Culture"], "hobby 1": ["S", "flew high-end drones for fun"], "training 1": ["S", "has a PhD in applied maths"], "name": ["S", "Tyler"]}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, "16": {"question": "Andie is a ballet dancer by training. During college, Andie studied painting and sculpting for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Andie works for a known tech company and collects Victor Hugo 1st editions.", "Andie works for a known tech company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects Victor Hugo 1st editions"], "work 1": ["S", "works for a known tech company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "studied painting and sculpting for fun"], "training 1": ["A", "is a ballet dancer by training"], "name": ["A", "Andie"]}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, "17": {"question": "Ari has a PhD in Art History. During college, Ari studied painting and sculpting for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Ari works for a known tech company and collects Victor Hugo 1st editions.", "Ari works for a known tech company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects Victor Hugo 1st editions"], "work 1": ["S", "works for a known tech company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "studied painting and sculpting for fun"], "training 1": ["A", "has a PhD in Art History"], "name": ["A", "Ari"]}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, "18": {"question": "Brook is a ballet dancer by training. During college, Brook wrote amateur novels online. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Brook works for a known tech company and collects Victor Hugo 1st editions.", "Brook works for a known tech company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects Victor Hugo 1st editions"], "work 1": ["S", "works for a known tech company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "wrote amateur novels online"], "training 1": ["A", "is a ballet dancer by training"], "name": ["A", "Brook"]}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, "19": {"question": "Dawson has a PhD in Art History. During college, Dawson wrote amateur novels online. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Dawson works for a known tech company and collects Victor Hugo 1st editions.", "Dawson works for a known tech company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects Victor Hugo 1st editions"], "work 1": ["S", "works for a known tech company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "wrote amateur novels online"], "training 1": ["A", "has a PhD in Art History"], "name": ["A", "Dawson"]}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, "20": {"question": "Cameron is a ballet dancer by training. During college, Cameron studied painting and sculpting for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Cameron is a logistics consultat for an important car company and collects Victor Hugo 1st editions.", "Cameron is a logistics consultat for an important car company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects Victor Hugo 1st editions"], "work 1": ["S", "is a logistics consultat for an important car company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "studied painting and sculpting for fun"], "training 1": ["A", "is a ballet dancer by training"], "name": ["A", "Cameron"]}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, "21": {"question": "Perry has a PhD in Art History. During college, Perry studied painting and sculpting for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Perry is a logistics consultat for an important car company and collects Victor Hugo 1st editions.", "Perry is a logistics consultat for an important car company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects Victor Hugo 1st editions"], "work 1": ["S", "is a logistics consultat for an important car company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "studied painting and sculpting for fun"], "training 1": ["A", "has a PhD in Art History"], "name": ["A", "Perry"]}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, "22": {"question": "Riley is a ballet dancer by training. During college, Riley wrote amateur novels online. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Riley is a logistics consultat for an important car company and collects Victor Hugo 1st editions.", "Riley is a logistics consultat for an important car company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects Victor Hugo 1st editions"], "work 1": ["S", "is a logistics consultat for an important car company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "wrote amateur novels online"], "training 1": ["A", "is a ballet dancer by training"], "name": ["A", "Riley"]}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, "23": {"question": "Sawyer has a PhD in Art History. During college, Sawyer wrote amateur novels online. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Sawyer is a logistics consultat for an important car company and collects Victor Hugo 1st editions.", "Sawyer is a logistics consultat for an important car company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects Victor Hugo 1st editions"], "work 1": ["S", "is a logistics consultat for an important car company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "wrote amateur novels online"], "training 1": ["A", "has a PhD in Art History"], "name": ["A", "Sawyer"]}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, "24": {"question": "Sloan is a ballet dancer by training. During college, Sloan studied painting and sculpting for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Sloan works for a known tech company and collects modern art.", "Sloan works for a known tech company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects modern art"], "work 1": ["S", "works for a known tech company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "studied painting and sculpting for fun"], "training 1": ["A", "is a ballet dancer by training"], "name": ["A", "Sloan"]}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, "25": {"question": "Rowan has a PhD in Art History. During college, Rowan studied painting and sculpting for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Rowan works for a known tech company and collects modern art.", "Rowan works for a known tech company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects modern art"], "work 1": ["S", "works for a known tech company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "studied painting and sculpting for fun"], "training 1": ["A", "has a PhD in Art History"], "name": ["A", "Rowan"]}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, "26": {"question": "Jude is a ballet dancer by training. During college, Jude wrote amateur novels online. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Jude works for a known tech company and collects modern art.", "Jude works for a known tech company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects modern art"], "work 1": ["S", "works for a known tech company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "wrote amateur novels online"], "training 1": ["A", "is a ballet dancer by training"], "name": ["A", "Jude"]}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, "27": {"question": "Maxwell has a PhD in Art History. During college, Maxwell wrote amateur novels online. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Maxwell works for a known tech company and collects modern art.", "Maxwell works for a known tech company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects modern art"], "work 1": ["S", "works for a known tech company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "wrote amateur novels online"], "training 1": ["A", "has a PhD in Art History"], "name": ["A", "Maxwell"]}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, "28": {"question": "River is a ballet dancer by training. During college, River studied painting and sculpting for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["River is a logistics consultat for an important car company and collects modern art.", "River is a logistics consultat for an important car company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects modern art"], "work 1": ["S", "is a logistics consultat for an important car company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "studied painting and sculpting for fun"], "training 1": ["A", "is a ballet dancer by training"], "name": ["A", "River"]}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, "29": {"question": "Morgan has a PhD in Art History. During college, Morgan studied painting and sculpting for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Morgan is a logistics consultat for an important car company and collects modern art.", "Morgan is a logistics consultat for an important car company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects modern art"], "work 1": ["S", "is a logistics consultat for an important car company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "studied painting and sculpting for fun"], "training 1": ["A", "has a PhD in Art History"], "name": ["A", "Morgan"]}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, "30": {"question": "Nicky is a ballet dancer by training. During college, Nicky wrote amateur novels online. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Nicky is a logistics consultat for an important car company and collects modern art.", "Nicky is a logistics consultat for an important car company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects modern art"], "work 1": ["S", "is a logistics consultat for an important car company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "wrote amateur novels online"], "training 1": ["A", "is a ballet dancer by training"], "name": ["A", "Nicky"]}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, "31": {"question": "Tyler has a PhD in Art History. During college, Tyler wrote amateur novels online. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Tyler is a logistics consultat for an important car company and collects modern art.", "Tyler is a logistics consultat for an important car company."], "info": {"order": 0, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects modern art"], "work 1": ["S", "is a logistics consultat for an important car company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "wrote amateur novels online"], "training 1": ["A", "has a PhD in Art History"], "name": ["A", "Tyler"]}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, "32": {"question": "Andie is a mechanical engineer by training. During college, Andie used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Andie is a consultant for the British Museum.", "Andie is a consultant for the British Museum and builds model airplanes as a hobby."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "builds model airplanes as a hobby"], "work 1": ["A", "is a consultant for the British Museum"], "hobby 1": ["S", "used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["S", "is a mechanical engineer by training"], "name": ["S", "Andie"]}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, "33": {"question": "Ari has a PhD in applied maths. During college, Ari used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Ari is a consultant for the British Museum.", "Ari is a consultant for the British Museum and builds model airplanes as a hobby."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "builds model airplanes as a hobby"], "work 1": ["A", "is a consultant for the British Museum"], "hobby 1": ["S", "used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["S", "has a PhD in applied maths"], "name": ["S", "Ari"]}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, "34": {"question": "Brook is a mechanical engineer by training. During college, Brook flew high-end drones for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Brook is a consultant for the British Museum.", "Brook is a consultant for the British Museum and builds model airplanes as a hobby."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "builds model airplanes as a hobby"], "work 1": ["A", "is a consultant for the British Museum"], "hobby 1": ["S", "flew high-end drones for fun"], "training 1": ["S", "is a mechanical engineer by training"], "name": ["S", "Brook"]}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, "35": {"question": "Dawson has a PhD in applied maths. During college, Dawson flew high-end drones for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Dawson is a consultant for the British Museum.", "Dawson is a consultant for the British Museum and builds model airplanes as a hobby."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "builds model airplanes as a hobby"], "work 1": ["A", "is a consultant for the British Museum"], "hobby 1": ["S", "flew high-end drones for fun"], "training 1": ["S", "has a PhD in applied maths"], "name": ["S", "Dawson"]}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, "36": {"question": "Cameron is a mechanical engineer by training. During college, Cameron used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Cameron is an advisor to the Minister of Culture.", "Cameron is an advisor to the Minister of Culture and builds model airplanes as a hobby."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "builds model airplanes as a hobby"], "work 1": ["A", "is an advisor to the Minister of Culture"], "hobby 1": ["S", "used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["S", "is a mechanical engineer by training"], "name": ["S", "Cameron"]}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, "37": {"question": "Perry has a PhD in applied maths. During college, Perry used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Perry is an advisor to the Minister of Culture.", "Perry is an advisor to the Minister of Culture and builds model airplanes as a hobby."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "builds model airplanes as a hobby"], "work 1": ["A", "is an advisor to the Minister of Culture"], "hobby 1": ["S", "used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["S", "has a PhD in applied maths"], "name": ["S", "Perry"]}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, "38": {"question": "Riley is a mechanical engineer by training. During college, Riley flew high-end drones for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Riley is an advisor to the Minister of Culture.", "Riley is an advisor to the Minister of Culture and builds model airplanes as a hobby."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "builds model airplanes as a hobby"], "work 1": ["A", "is an advisor to the Minister of Culture"], "hobby 1": ["S", "flew high-end drones for fun"], "training 1": ["S", "is a mechanical engineer by training"], "name": ["S", "Riley"]}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, "39": {"question": "Sawyer has a PhD in applied maths. During college, Sawyer flew high-end drones for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Sawyer is an advisor to the Minister of Culture.", "Sawyer is an advisor to the Minister of Culture and builds model airplanes as a hobby."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "builds model airplanes as a hobby"], "work 1": ["A", "is an advisor to the Minister of Culture"], "hobby 1": ["S", "flew high-end drones for fun"], "training 1": ["S", "has a PhD in applied maths"], "name": ["S", "Sawyer"]}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, "40": {"question": "Sloan is a mechanical engineer by training. During college, Sloan used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Sloan is a consultant for the British Museum.", "Sloan is a consultant for the British Museum and plays Go, during spare time."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "plays Go, during spare time"], "work 1": ["A", "is a consultant for the British Museum"], "hobby 1": ["S", "used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["S", "is a mechanical engineer by training"], "name": ["S", "Sloan"]}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, "41": {"question": "Rowan has a PhD in applied maths. During college, Rowan used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Rowan is a consultant for the British Museum.", "Rowan is a consultant for the British Museum and plays Go, during spare time."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "plays Go, during spare time"], "work 1": ["A", "is a consultant for the British Museum"], "hobby 1": ["S", "used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["S", "has a PhD in applied maths"], "name": ["S", "Rowan"]}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, "42": {"question": "Jude is a mechanical engineer by training. During college, Jude flew high-end drones for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Jude is a consultant for the British Museum.", "Jude is a consultant for the British Museum and plays Go, during spare time."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "plays Go, during spare time"], "work 1": ["A", "is a consultant for the British Museum"], "hobby 1": ["S", "flew high-end drones for fun"], "training 1": ["S", "is a mechanical engineer by training"], "name": ["S", "Jude"]}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, "43": {"question": "Maxwell has a PhD in applied maths. During college, Maxwell flew high-end drones for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Maxwell is a consultant for the British Museum.", "Maxwell is a consultant for the British Museum and plays Go, during spare time."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "plays Go, during spare time"], "work 1": ["A", "is a consultant for the British Museum"], "hobby 1": ["S", "flew high-end drones for fun"], "training 1": ["S", "has a PhD in applied maths"], "name": ["S", "Maxwell"]}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, "44": {"question": "River is a mechanical engineer by training. During college, River used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["River is an advisor to the Minister of Culture.", "River is an advisor to the Minister of Culture and plays Go, during spare time."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "plays Go, during spare time"], "work 1": ["A", "is an advisor to the Minister of Culture"], "hobby 1": ["S", "used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["S", "is a mechanical engineer by training"], "name": ["S", "River"]}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, "45": {"question": "Morgan has a PhD in applied maths. During college, Morgan used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Morgan is an advisor to the Minister of Culture.", "Morgan is an advisor to the Minister of Culture and plays Go, during spare time."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "plays Go, during spare time"], "work 1": ["A", "is an advisor to the Minister of Culture"], "hobby 1": ["S", "used to collect minerals and cristals, as a hobby"], "training 1": ["S", "has a PhD in applied maths"], "name": ["S", "Morgan"]}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, "46": {"question": "Nicky is a mechanical engineer by training. During college, Nicky flew high-end drones for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Nicky is an advisor to the Minister of Culture.", "Nicky is an advisor to the Minister of Culture and plays Go, during spare time."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "plays Go, during spare time"], "work 1": ["A", "is an advisor to the Minister of Culture"], "hobby 1": ["S", "flew high-end drones for fun"], "training 1": ["S", "is a mechanical engineer by training"], "name": ["S", "Nicky"]}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, "47": {"question": "Tyler has a PhD in applied maths. During college, Tyler flew high-end drones for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Tyler is an advisor to the Minister of Culture.", "Tyler is an advisor to the Minister of Culture and plays Go, during spare time."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["S", "plays Go, during spare time"], "work 1": ["A", "is an advisor to the Minister of Culture"], "hobby 1": ["S", "flew high-end drones for fun"], "training 1": ["S", "has a PhD in applied maths"], "name": ["S", "Tyler"]}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, "48": {"question": "Andie is a ballet dancer by training. During college, Andie studied painting and sculpting for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Andie works for a known tech company.", "Andie works for a known tech company and collects Victor Hugo 1st editions."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects Victor Hugo 1st editions"], "work 1": ["S", "works for a known tech company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "studied painting and sculpting for fun"], "training 1": ["A", "is a ballet dancer by training"], "name": ["A", "Andie"]}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, "49": {"question": "Ari has a PhD in Art History. During college, Ari studied painting and sculpting for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Ari works for a known tech company.", "Ari works for a known tech company and collects Victor Hugo 1st editions."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects Victor Hugo 1st editions"], "work 1": ["S", "works for a known tech company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "studied painting and sculpting for fun"], "training 1": ["A", "has a PhD in Art History"], "name": ["A", "Ari"]}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, "50": {"question": "Brook is a ballet dancer by training. During college, Brook wrote amateur novels online. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Brook works for a known tech company.", "Brook works for a known tech company and collects Victor Hugo 1st editions."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects Victor Hugo 1st editions"], "work 1": ["S", "works for a known tech company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "wrote amateur novels online"], "training 1": ["A", "is a ballet dancer by training"], "name": ["A", "Brook"]}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, "51": {"question": "Dawson has a PhD in Art History. During college, Dawson wrote amateur novels online. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Dawson works for a known tech company.", "Dawson works for a known tech company and collects Victor Hugo 1st editions."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects Victor Hugo 1st editions"], "work 1": ["S", "works for a known tech company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "wrote amateur novels online"], "training 1": ["A", "has a PhD in Art History"], "name": ["A", "Dawson"]}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, "52": {"question": "Cameron is a ballet dancer by training. During college, Cameron studied painting and sculpting for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Cameron is a logistics consultat for an important car company.", "Cameron is a logistics consultat for an important car company and collects Victor Hugo 1st editions."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects Victor Hugo 1st editions"], "work 1": ["S", "is a logistics consultat for an important car company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "studied painting and sculpting for fun"], "training 1": ["A", "is a ballet dancer by training"], "name": ["A", "Cameron"]}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, "53": {"question": "Perry has a PhD in Art History. During college, Perry studied painting and sculpting for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Perry is a logistics consultat for an important car company.", "Perry is a logistics consultat for an important car company and collects Victor Hugo 1st editions."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects Victor Hugo 1st editions"], "work 1": ["S", "is a logistics consultat for an important car company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "studied painting and sculpting for fun"], "training 1": ["A", "has a PhD in Art History"], "name": ["A", "Perry"]}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, "54": {"question": "Riley is a ballet dancer by training. During college, Riley wrote amateur novels online. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Riley is a logistics consultat for an important car company.", "Riley is a logistics consultat for an important car company and collects Victor Hugo 1st editions."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects Victor Hugo 1st editions"], "work 1": ["S", "is a logistics consultat for an important car company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "wrote amateur novels online"], "training 1": ["A", "is a ballet dancer by training"], "name": ["A", "Riley"]}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, "55": {"question": "Sawyer has a PhD in Art History. During college, Sawyer wrote amateur novels online. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Sawyer is a logistics consultat for an important car company.", "Sawyer is a logistics consultat for an important car company and collects Victor Hugo 1st editions."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects Victor Hugo 1st editions"], "work 1": ["S", "is a logistics consultat for an important car company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "wrote amateur novels online"], "training 1": ["A", "has a PhD in Art History"], "name": ["A", "Sawyer"]}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, "56": {"question": "Sloan is a ballet dancer by training. During college, Sloan studied painting and sculpting for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Sloan works for a known tech company.", "Sloan works for a known tech company and collects modern art."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects modern art"], "work 1": ["S", "works for a known tech company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "studied painting and sculpting for fun"], "training 1": ["A", "is a ballet dancer by training"], "name": ["A", "Sloan"]}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, "57": {"question": "Rowan has a PhD in Art History. During college, Rowan studied painting and sculpting for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Rowan works for a known tech company.", "Rowan works for a known tech company and collects modern art."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects modern art"], "work 1": ["S", "works for a known tech company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "studied painting and sculpting for fun"], "training 1": ["A", "has a PhD in Art History"], "name": ["A", "Rowan"]}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, "58": {"question": "Jude is a ballet dancer by training. During college, Jude wrote amateur novels online. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Jude works for a known tech company.", "Jude works for a known tech company and collects modern art."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects modern art"], "work 1": ["S", "works for a known tech company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "wrote amateur novels online"], "training 1": ["A", "is a ballet dancer by training"], "name": ["A", "Jude"]}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, "59": {"question": "Maxwell has a PhD in Art History. During college, Maxwell wrote amateur novels online. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Maxwell works for a known tech company.", "Maxwell works for a known tech company and collects modern art."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects modern art"], "work 1": ["S", "works for a known tech company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "wrote amateur novels online"], "training 1": ["A", "has a PhD in Art History"], "name": ["A", "Maxwell"]}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, "60": {"question": "River is a ballet dancer by training. During college, River studied painting and sculpting for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["River is a logistics consultat for an important car company.", "River is a logistics consultat for an important car company and collects modern art."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects modern art"], "work 1": ["S", "is a logistics consultat for an important car company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "studied painting and sculpting for fun"], "training 1": ["A", "is a ballet dancer by training"], "name": ["A", "River"]}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, "61": {"question": "Morgan has a PhD in Art History. During college, Morgan studied painting and sculpting for fun. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Morgan is a logistics consultat for an important car company.", "Morgan is a logistics consultat for an important car company and collects modern art."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects modern art"], "work 1": ["S", "is a logistics consultat for an important car company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "studied painting and sculpting for fun"], "training 1": ["A", "has a PhD in Art History"], "name": ["A", "Morgan"]}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, "62": {"question": "Nicky is a ballet dancer by training. During college, Nicky wrote amateur novels online. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Nicky is a logistics consultat for an important car company.", "Nicky is a logistics consultat for an important car company and collects modern art."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects modern art"], "work 1": ["S", "is a logistics consultat for an important car company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "wrote amateur novels online"], "training 1": ["A", "is a ballet dancer by training"], "name": ["A", "Nicky"]}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}, "63": {"question": "Tyler has a PhD in Art History. During college, Tyler wrote amateur novels online. Ten years later, which of these two scenarios is more probable ?", "answers": ["Tyler is a logistics consultat for an important car company.", "Tyler is a logistics consultat for an important car company and collects modern art."], "info": {"order": 1, "hobby 2": ["A", "collects modern art"], "work 1": ["S", "is a logistics consultat for an important car company"], "hobby 1": ["A", "wrote amateur novels online"], "training 1": ["A", "has a PhD in Art History"], "name": ["A", "Tyler"]}, "keywords": {"first": [], "second": []}}}